Finding Aid for the Panoramic Photographs Collection LSC.0649
UCLA Library Special Collections
Panoramic Photographs collection
1906-1966
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.0649
513.0 Linear Feet (171 map folders)
Collection consists of black and white panoramic photographs; subject matter is mostly California and the Western United States.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Photographs were either removed from Picture Collection (Collection 99) or purchased by UCLA Library Special Collections.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9956512173606533
Scope and Content
Collection consists of black and white panoramic photographs; subject matter is mostly California and the Western United States. Folder titles reflect inscriptions on the photographs, information transcribed from verso, or the photograph's subject matter.
Related Material
Picture Collection (Collection 99). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections.
California -- Photographs.; West (U.S.) -- Photographs.; Panoramic photographs.
- 1) [Loyola University, Los Angeles, School of Law and Views, California]., 1907
- 2) [Hercules, Arizona]., 1909
- 3) On the Mendocino Coast [California]., 1911
- 4) Redlands, [California]., 1907
- 5) [Palm Canyon, Palm Springs, California]., 1907
- 6) In the Canyon of a Thousand Palms [California]., 1907
- 7) [Bird's Eye of San Diego, California]., [1911]
- 8) Midway Point, Monterey [California]., 1906
- 9) Ruins of San Francisquito Reservoir [Los Angeles, California]., 1928 March 20
- 10) [Rhyolite, Nevada]., 1907
- 11) [California]., 1908
- 12) [Rubido Mountain, Riverside, California]., 1908
- 13) [Riverside, California]., 1908
- 14) Santa Barbara [California]., 1907
- 15) [Santa Monica Canyon, California]., 1908
- 16) [Panama Pacific International Exposition, San Francisco, California]., 1914 March
- 17) [Panama Pacific International Exposition, San Francisco, California]., 1914 March 27
- 18) [Bird's eye view of Panama Pacific International Exposition, San Francisco, California]., 1914
- 19) [Panama Pacific International Exposition, taken from south gardens, San Francisco, California]., 1914 June 21
- 20) [Panama Pacific International Exposition, panorama taken from Vallejo Street, San Francisco, California]., 1914
- 21) [Panama Pacific International Exposition, San Francisco, California]., 1915 Mar 1
- 22) Along the Shore, Tahoe Point, Lake Tahoe [California]., 1906
- 23) Lake Tahoe from Tahoe Point [California]., 1907
- 24) Panorama of Tahoe Tavern and Lake Tahoe [California]., 1906
- 25) Cascade Lake near Lake Tahoe [California]., 1906
- 26) [Grass Lake, Lake Tahoe, California]., 1910
- 27) [Cascade Lake, Lake Tahoe from Emerald Bay Ridge, California]., 1910
- 28) [Heather Lake, Lake Tahoe]., 1910
- 29) [Glen Alpine Country, Lake Tahoe, California]., [1910]
- 30) [Desolation Valley, Lake Tahoe, California]., [1910 July 25]
- 31) Panorama of Lake Tahoe from Mt. Tallac [California]., 1906
- 32) [Tahoe Tavern and casino from the pier, Lake Tahoe, California]., 1910
- 33) [Mt. Tallac from the Lilly Ponds, Lake Tahoe, California]., [1910]
- 34) [Bright Angel Trail, Grand Canyon, Arizona]., 1909
- 35) [Grand Canyon, Arizona]., [1921]
- 36) Columbia Gardens [Butte, Montana]., 1914
- 37) [Estes Park, Colorado]., [1917]
- 38) Ewing Field, Opening of San Francisco New Baseball Park, May 16th 1914, 17,500 Fans Assembled [California].
- 39) El Capitan, Yosemite National Park [California]., 1906
- 40) Mt. Watkins in Mirror Lake [Yosemite National Park, California]., 1907
- 41) Cascade Falls, Yosemite [California]., 1907
- 42) Twin Sisters [Redwood views, California]., [1915]
- 43) [Roosevelt Dam, Arizona]., 1920
- 44) [Crossing the Roosevelt Dam, Arizona]., 1920
- 45) Mariposa Big Tree Grove [Redwood views, California]., 1906
- 46) Mariposa Big Tree Grove [Redwood views, California]., 1906
- 47) Nature's Wonderland, California Redwoods [Humboldt County, California]., 1913
- 48) [Big Trees at cabin, Mariposa Big Tree Grove, Redwood views, California]., [1908]
- 49) The Tree of Ages [Redwood views, California]., [1915]
- 50) The Undercut [Redwood views, California]., [1915]
- 51) [Roosevelt Dam and road, Arizona]., 1920
- 52) Bridal Veil Falls [Yosemite National Park, Arizona]., 1907
- 53) Bridal Veil Falls [Yosemite National Park, Arizona]., 1907
- 54) Boole [Redwood views, California]., [1915]
- 55) The Cloistered Aisle [California Redwood Park]., 1906
- 56) Panorama of Yosemite Valley from Artists Point [California]., 1906
- 57) The Mother of the Forest [California Redwood Park]., 1906
- 58) General Lee [Redwood views, California]., 1906
- 59) [Power House, Roosevelt Dam site, Arizona]., 1907
- 60) View at El Portal, Yosemite Valley Railroad Terminus [California]., [1908]
- 61) Yosemite Valley from Artists Point [California]., [1911]
- 62) [Roosevelt Dam, Roosevelt, Arizona]., 1907
- 63) [Dedication, Santa Monica City Hall, California]., 1939
  Scope and Contents note
  Print (w/ negative).
- 64) [Dedication, Santa Monica City Hall, California]., 1939
  Negative.
- 65) Lake Hollywood, A Glittering Gem [Los Angeles, California]., n.d.
- 66) [Vetren townsite, Nevada]., [1912]
- 67) [Long Beach, California]., 1924
- 68) Tanforan., 1911
- 69) War Relocation Center, Manzanar California., 1943
- 70) General Grant Tree, Mariposa Grove [Redwood views, California]., 1906
- 71) Near Cypress Point, 17 Mile Drive, Monterey [California]., 1906
- 72) Third Biennial National Japanese American Citizens League Convention. San Francisco California., 1934 August 31
- 73) Westlake Park, A Delightful Oasis. Los Angeles, California., n.d.
- 74) Japanese American Citizens League Fifth Biennial National Convention, September 1-5 1938. Los Angeles, California.
- 75) [Santa Monica Canyon looking west from back of Westwood, California]., n.d.
- 76) Palisades del Rey [Santa Monica, California]., 1925 July 19
- 77) M.M. Co's Gravel Train., [1913]
- 78) [Picnic of Los Angeles Barber's Union, White Point, California]., 1923 July 5
- 79) Japanese American Citizen League 19th Biennial National Convention, July 26-30 1966. San Diego, California.
- 80) [Fish Creek Canyon, Arizona]., 1909
- 81) Third Annual Southern District Japanese American Citizen League Convention, San Diego California, July 4-5 1937.
- 82) Shohone Falls [Snake River, Idaho]., 1913
- 83) [Miami Shafts, Oklahoma?]., 1909
- 84) [Lower Red Fish Lake, California]., [1911]
- 85) [The Superior and Boston Company]., 1909
- 86) [California?]., [1915]
- 87) [Oil field, California?]., [1910]
- 88) Panorama of Orange Groves [California]., [1914]
- 89) [Sun Basin, Arizona]., 1909
- 90) [Timber land on Heffern claim]., 1909
- 91) [Mountains north of Santa Monica Canyon, California]., 1910
- 92) Xth Olympiad Committee., 1932
- 93) Rand District California, from Red Mountain, June 1922.
- 94) [Hermosa Oil Field]., 1930 November 8
- 95) [Heffern claim]., 1909
- 96) Hostesses of the Foreign Bungalows, House of Pacific Relations, Balboa Park, San Diego [California].
- 97) 153rd General Assembly, Presbyterian Church in the United Sates of America, St. Louis Missouri, May 22-28, 1941.
- 98) [Beanfield, Marinette Land Company]., 1912
- 99) [Los Angeles aqueduct and Grays camp, California]., [1912]
- 100) Panorma d' Assisi [Italy?]., n.d.
  General note
  Joseph Scott collection.
- 101) [Lake, lodge and mountains]., [1909]
- 102) [Mt. Vrain?, Glacier, Colorado]., [1921]
- 103) Panorama of Mt. Tacoma from Paradise Valley [Washington]., 1906
- 104) Panorama of Mt. Tacoma from Paradise Valley [Washington]., 1906
- 105) Nisqually Glacier, Mt. Tacoma, 14,519 feet from Paradise Valley [Washington]., 1906
- 106) Nisqually Glacier, Mt. Tacoma, 14,519 feet from Paradise Valley [Washington]., 1906
- 107) Country Club at American Lake Near Tacoma [Washington]., 1906
- 108) American Lake near Tacoma [Washington]., 1906
- 109) Mt. Ranier from Eagle Peak [Washington]., 1907
- 110) [Annual outdoor exhibition public schools, Tacoma Washington, May 19, 1913].
- 111) [Lake View property and 25 Hill, Oil field views, California]., [1910]
- 112) Driving First Pile, Hill Terminals, Flavel, Oregon., June 3-14, 1914
- 113) Flavel-Warrenton and Astoria, Oregon., 1914
- 114) Crater Lake, Oregon., 1913
  Weston[?].
- 115) Camp Jackson - Gearhart, Oregon., 1914
- 116) East Oregon Shipbuilding Camp., 1941
- 117) 26th Annual Congress of National Society 'Sons of the American Revolution,' Portland Oregon, July 21 1915.
- 118) Floating Clouds at Mirror Lake [Banff National Park, Canada]., 1906
- 119) [Petrified Forest, Arizona]., [1908]
- 120) [Petrified Forest, Arizona]., [1908]
- 121) [Petrified Forest, Arizona]., [1908]
- 122) [Ray Mineral Zone, Arizona]., 1908
- 123) [Queen Creek Sheep Shearing Camp, Arizona]., 1908
- 124) [Sheep scene, Arizona]., 1908
- 125) [Ray and Hercules Mines, Arizona]., 1909
- 126) [Hotel at Fish Creek, Arizona]., 1909
- 127) [Ray Mineral Zone, Arizona]., 1908
- 128) [Everett, Washington]., 1912
- 129) The Asulkan Glacier from Glacier Crest [Washington]., 1906
- 130) Panorama from Saddleback Glacier [Washington]., 1906
- 131) Emerald Lake (near Field B.C.) from the trail to Yoho [Washington]., 1906
- 132) Lake Chelan, in the Cascade Mountains, Washington., 1907
- 133) [Guantanamo Bay]., n.d.; (Color)
- 134) Guantanamo Bay and United States Naval Station.
- 135) Regiment United States Atlantic Fleet, Deer Point Camp, Guantanamo Bay. February 1910.
- 136) Panorama Showing First, Second, and Third Regiments United States Marines. Deer Point Camp, Guantanamo Bay, Cuba, April 26, 1911.
- 137) [Shipyard]., n.d.
- 138) [View from Gribble Ranch]., 1915
- 139) [Little lake looking northwest]., [1915]
- 140) The Century of Progress, Chicago, Illinois, 1934 [Chicago World's Fair].
- 141) [Grand Canyon National Park and Colorado River, Arizona]., [1908]
- 142) [Ray, Arizona]., [1909]
- 143) Raymond Hotel and Golf Links, Pasadena, California., [1915]
- 144) [View from Hollingsworth Building, looking southeast]., [1915]
- 145) [Long Beach, California]., [1920s]
- 146a;b) [Kelvin, Arizona]., [1909]
  Two identical photographs.
- 147) Stanford - 13 vs. USC - 9, Attendance 74,000, October 17, 1925 [California].
- 148a;b) Governor Johnson and party in the Redwoods [California]., 1916
- 149) [Malibu Canyon, Mouth of Malibu Canyon-Sierra Road, Malibu Pier extreme right California]., n.d.
- 150) [Downtown Los Angeles, California]., n.d.
- 151) [Santa Monica Canyon North, California]., [1929]
- 152) [Venice, California]., [1918]
- 153) [San Francisco Panama Pacific International Exposition, California]., 1914
- 154) View of Brawley, California, June 1913.
- 155) Lights and Shades, Redwood (Sequoia Semperviren) Forest [California]., 1915
- 156) Silverlake District, It Has Everything, Los Angeles, California., n.d.
- 157) Hong Kong., n.d.
- 158) [Mission to San Juan Capistrano, California]., [1916]
- 159) [San Francisco Panama Pacific International Exposition, California]., 1914
- 160) Official Opening and Dedication, United Airport, May 30, 1930 [Burbank, California].
- 161) [Hemet, California]., 1915
- 162) [Beverly Boulevard and La Brea Street, Los Angeles, California]., 1916
- 163) Rancho La Brea Oil Company [3rd and La Brea Streets, Los Angeles, California]., 1916
- 164) [Tehachapi Loop, Southern Pacific Railroad, California]., 1910
- 165a;b) [Fish Creek, Arizona]., 1909
- 166) [Marinette townsite, Arizona]., [1912]
- 167) 'Driving the Golden Spike' Northwestern Pacific Railroad, Cain Rock, October 23rd 1914 [California].
- 168) [Downtown Los Angeles], Lloyd Photo Company, Los Angeles, California., 1914
- 169) Annual Board Meeting Southern California Committee for the Olympic Games, California Club, March 18, 1947.
- 170a;b;c) Luncheon, Centennial Anniversary of Discovery of Gold in California, Native Sons and Daughters of the Golden West, January 24, 1948. Biltmore Hotel, Los Angeles [California].
  Three identical photographs.
- 171) Main buildings, Panama Pacific International Exposition. San Francisco, California., 1914
- 172a;b) Sunset Club, Christmas Jinx, California Club, December 26, 1930.
- 173) Sunset Club, Christmas Jinx, California Club, December 29, 1931.
- 174) Sunset Club, Christmas Jinx, California Club, December 28, 1934.
- 175) 40th Anniversary, Sunset Club, Los Angeles, California, May 31st 1935.
- 176) Sunset Club, Christmas Jinx, California Club, December 27, 1935.
- 177) [Harbor, France]., n.d.
  Print (with illustrated overlay).
- 178) [Harbor, France]., n.d.
  Illustrated overlay.
- 179) Progress Dinner of United Business Interests to the Aviation Industry under the auspices of the National Exchange Club, Hotel Commodore, New York, January 29, 1929.
  ex libris W.W. Hodkinson.
- 180) The Late Watch Dinner, 37 Years After, San Francisco Press Club, April 17, 1943 [California].
  ex libris Edward A. Dickson.
- 181) Sunset Club, Christmas Jinx, December 26, 1941.
- 182) East Los Angeles, California January 29, 1946 Pettit's Studio 1416 W. Pico, Los Angeles.
  General
  Atlantic Avenue looking north and Whittier Boulevard looking west.
- 183) Hollywood Los Angeles Pierce, 1910
  Hollywood looking southwest from Vermont Avenue and Franklin Avenue.
- 184) [Long Beach, California in the 1920s] The Aerograph Co. [Los Angeles, Calif.]
- 185) [Workers and vehicles of the transportation department of the Chanslor-Canfield Midway Oil Company (CCMO) in Torrance, California]. C.G. Duffey Photo, 511 E. 6th St., Long Beach, Calif., 1924
- 186) Intérieur de la Mosquée de Ste Sophie. [Istanbul, Turkey]: Sébah & Joaillier, [1890?]
- 187) [Panoramic photograph of San Francisco in the 1920s]. Waters Company, photographer., [between 1921-1926]
- 188) [Panoramic photograph of Stone Town, Zanzibar]., [approximately 1900]
- 189) [Panoramic photograph of Constantinople taken from the Galata Tower]., [between 1880 and 1889]
- 190) [Panoramic photograph of the port and harbor of Vladivostok, Russia]., [approximately 1900]